<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>SEC Schedule 13D Item 4 (Fast Alert Enhanced)</title>
<link>https://www.sec.gov</link>
<description>Item 4 from SC 13D and 13D/A filings containing buyout-related keywords</description>
<item>
<title>[AMENDED] 🔄 SilverCape (SC 13D/A)</title>
<link>https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1040130/000121390025120354/xslSCHEDULE_13D_X01/primary_doc.xml</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:08:08 -0000</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Â 
Item 4 of the Prior Statement is hereby amended and supplemented to add the following:

On December 10, 2025, <strong>SilverCape</strong> sent a Letter re: Non-Binding Proposal for Potential Transaction (the "Letter") to the Issuer providing a non-binding proposal (the "Proposal") to take the Issuer private by acquiring <strong>100%</strong> of the Issuer's outstanding Common Stock at a price of $4.00 per share of Common Stock in cash (the "Potential Transaction"). The Proposal states that the purchase price for the Potential Transaction would be funded with <strong>SilverCape</strong>'s cash on hand and that the Potential Transaction would not be subject to any financing conditions or contingencies.

The Proposal for the Potential Transaction was (and remains) non-binding and is subject in all respects to, among other things: (a) the Reporting Persons' further due diligence (including, but not limited to, financial, tax, accounting, legal, compliance, human resources, IT and regulatory due diligence) and (b) the execution of a mutually acceptable definitive agreement with terms and conditions customary for transactions of the type contemplated by the Proposal (the "Definitive Agreement"), including, without limitation, that the Issuer and its board of directors take all actions necessary to render inapplicable the Issuer's shareholder rights plan or other similar anti<strong>takeover</strong> protections that are or could become applicable in connection with the transactions contemplated by the Letter, the Potential Transaction or the Definitive Agreement.

As provided in the Letter, the Reporting Persons are seeking to commence due diligence and the preparation of the Definitive Agreement as soon as possible.

The foregoing description of the Letter is not intended to be complete and is qualified in its entirety by reference to the full text of the Letter, which is filed as Exhibit 99.2 to this Amendment No. 1 and is incorporated herein by reference.

There can be no assurance that a Definitive Agreement with respect to the Potential Transaction will be executed or, if executed, whether the Potential Transaction will be consummated. No legally binding obligation with respect to the Proposal or the Potential Transaction will arise until such time, if ever, as a binding Definitive Agreement has been executed by the relevant parties. There is also no certainty as to whether, or when, the Issuer may respond to the Letter, or as to the time table for execution of any Definitive Agreement. The Reporting Persons reserves the right to modify or withdraw the Proposal at any time and to cease discussions and negotiations at any time. Neither the Letter nor this Schedule 13D is meant to be an offer to purchase or a solicitation of any offer to sell shares of the Issuer's Common Stock or other securities.

The Reporting Persons intend to engage in discussions with the Issuer regarding the Potential Transaction. The Reporting Persons may change the terms of the Proposal or the Potential Transaction, determine to accelerate or terminate discussions with the Issuer with respect to the Potential Transaction, withdraw the Proposal described in the Letter or any other proposal with respect to the Potential Transaction, take any action to facilitate or increase the likelihood of consummation of the Potential Transaction, or change their intentions with respect to any such matters, in each case at any time and without prior notice. The Reporting Persons reserve the right to, directly or indirectly, take such additional steps as they may deem appropriate to further the Potential Transaction or otherwise to support their investment in the Issuer, including, without limitation: (a) engaging in discussions with other shareholders, advisors and other relevant parties; and (b) entering into confidentiality arrangements, and other agreements, arrangements and understandings in connection with the Potential Transaction.

The Potential Transaction may result in one or more of the actions specified in clauses (a) to (j) of Item 4 of Schedule 13D, including, without limitation, the acquisition of additional securities of the Issuer, a merger or other extraordinary transaction involving the Issuer, the delisting of the Common Stock from the Nasdaq and the Common Stock becoming eligible for termination of registration pursuant to Section 12(g)(4) of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended.

The Reporting Persons intend to review their existing investment in the Issuer on a continuing basis. Depending on the Reporting Persons' evaluation of various factors, including, without limitation, the outcome of any discussions referenced above, the Company's financial position, results and strategic direction, actions taken by the Company's management and the Board, price levels of the Common Stock and other investment opportunities available to the Reporting Persons, compliance with applicable laws, general market and economic conditions, ongoing evaluation of the Issuer's business, financial condition, operations and prospects, the relative attractiveness of alternative business and investment opportunities, the Reporting Persons' need for liquidity, and other future developments, the Reporting Persons may in the future take such actions with respect to their investment in the Issuer as they deem appropriate, including, without limitation, acquiring shares of Common Stock and/or other equity or other securities of the Company or disposing of some or all of the securities beneficially owned by the Reporting Persons in public market or privately negotiated transactions, formulating other plans or proposals regarding the Issuer or its securities to the extent deemed advisable by the Reporting Persons, and/or otherwise changing their intention with respect to any and all matters referred to in Item 4 of this Schedule 13D.]]></description>
</item>
</channel></rss>